Today I will teach you how to make a real window ring on clothing.
First, let's put this ring that has been done.
Add in.
Then make it an added option.
You must choose a virtual model for the object type to have a real conflict.
Then after this ring is added in, we can see it in the position on this ground.
And you can also see it on the window of the second floor.
We are now going to use a replacement thinking to make it.
Because if you wear it directly, it is easy to simulate instability.
What is the replacement thinking?
It's the position of our neck now.
Sew a ring with this ring.
A round piece of almost the same size.
Then put this ring in the middle.
Now let's make a round piece.
Then you can draw according to the size of this ring in the window of the second floor.
The appearance of this shadow is related to the placement of the board in the 3D window.
It is a square in the center of a cross on our ground.
Hide this virtual model first.
Then take a look at our ground.
There is a cross center.
It corresponds to our plane.
If you move this ring to the front or the back, you can't see it.
Then you can also use this ring.
In the attribute editor, the value of this XY is 53 mm.
You can also directly create a round piece.
Draw a 53.
Then change the size of this board piece to a small one.
This way, it can be turned into a circle.
We can move this board piece to the appropriate position on the top.
Then show our model.
Then in 3D, go back to the 2D arrangement position to choose.
You can quickly get to this center position.
Now let's adjust its position.
We use this world coordinate to adjust it.
Look at it in many angles.
Finally, you need to look at the side.
Because if you want a natural穿着.
Finally, it must be with our virtual model.
This arc is a parallel state.
So we will try to switch to semi-transparent.
The surface of semi-transparent.
Then press 4 or 6.
Switch to the side of the model.
Then rotate.
You can see that it is in this position.
It's almost like this.
I just accidentally moved it over.
It needs to be moved back.
Switch to the surface of dense texture.
This side.
The thickness of this fabric has been changed to 2mm in advance.
So this board piece looks a little thick.
Then we can sew it with our position.
Don't simulate after sewing.
Freeze this board piece.
Then simulate.
After simulation.
We can see this board piece.
It's actually the same size as our circle.
Now put this circle over.
Press this quick arrangement tool.
Put it in this place.
You can push it in a little bit more.
We finally need to wrap the board piece around the circle.
So we're going to shrink this board piece a little bit.
Put this circle back into the virtual model first.
Don't let it affect our simulation.
Then double-click to activate the cross center of this board piece.
Let the board piece be shrunk according to the center point.
Then simulate.
You can see that this board piece is now overlapping with the circle.
Next.
We can cut the dragon layer of the board piece.
Add this circle to the double-layer board piece.
Simulate.
Then adjust the sewing line.
Delete these sewing lines first.
Then we delete this sewing line first.
Then sew it up in sections.
This point is aligned with the outside of the board piece.
Then add this point.
Align it to the outside of the board piece and add a point.
Because we want to record it here.
After aligning, we can sew it.
Change to a fold.
Here we don't sew first.
Sew the inside.
Next.
Sew the bottom.
Then simulate.
Now activate this circle.
Activate virtual model.
Then adjust the layer relationship with our grid tool in this position.
Select the frame.
Then 3D window points out the positioning ball.
Pull the blue axis.
We first hide this model for a moment.
From the back.
It is also the same frame.
Pull it after selecting.
Then for the stability of our simulation.
We will reduce the particle diameter of these two boards to 5.
Then reduce the surface diameter of the circle to 0.
The conflict thickness of these two boards has been adjusted.
Now we simulate again.
Now it is already in a state of wearing.
If there are some penetrations.
We can even reduce the particle diameter of the board piece to 3.
It can solve the penetrating problem.
After this step.
This circle has completed its mission.
Can be deleted.
Then simulate again.
You can see that our current version.
It is truly wrapped in the state of the circle.
Finally, we sew this place again.
We can see that the position of this circle is actually a bit high.
So this place is arched.
We can adjust it by opening the simulation again.
When simulating.
Use this positioning ball.
Slowly adjust its position.
To adjust a little bit.
This is the position.
You can see that.
Its current shape.
It is a relatively natural state.
Sometimes.
In fact.
This ring.
It's not two-layer board.
Just the one-layer board.
Over-folded.
Then we can get this board.
Cut off.
We delete the unnecessary seam allowances
Just re-add the seam allowances
Simulate again
It's done
The above is the production method explanation of our real ring
Thank you for watching